1. Recode all examples;

2. Please combine image crop, color shift, rotation and perspective transform together to complete a data augmentation script.
   Your code need to be completed in Python/C++ in .py or .cpp file with comments and readme file to indicate how to use.

3. Do think about your own interests very carefully and choose your topic within 3 weeks.

4. 【Please send answers to those questions to mqgao@kaikeba.com】
   Please answer some questions about our course. We do appreciate your help.
   4.1 What do you want to get in this course?
   4.2 What problems do you want to solve?
   4.3 What advantages do you have to accomplish your goal?
   4.4 What disadvantages you need to overcome to accomplish your goal?
   4.5 How will you plan to study in this course?
   